/*---------------------------Questions for Beginner Level------------------------*/
/*-------------------------------------------------------------------------------*/
window.gameBeginnerLevelQuestions = [
    {
        question: "1 + 2 = 3",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "Yes",
        correctAnswer: 3,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "3 + 4 = 8",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: 7,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "4 * 4 = 17",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: 16,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "5 * 4 = 20",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "Yes",
        correctAnswer: 20,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "12 / 4 = 3",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "Yes",
        correctAnswer: 3,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "6 - 6 = -1",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: 0,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "5 * 4 = 20",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "Yes",
        correctAnswer: 20,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "15 * 4 = 55",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: 60,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "19 + 21 = 50",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: 40,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "64 / 2 = 34",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: 32,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "9 - 5 = 4",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "Yes",
        correctAnswer: 4,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "13 + 7 = 20",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "Yes",
        correctAnswer: 20,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "4 * 8 = 50",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: 40,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "2 * 2 = 4",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "Yes",
        correctAnswer: 4,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "1 * 0 = 1",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: 0,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "12 + 4 = 18",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: 16,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "13 - 4 = 9",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "Yes",
        correctAnswer: 9,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "12 * 4 = 36",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: 48,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "12 * 12 = 144",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "Yes",
        correctAnswer: 144,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "-1 * 2 = -1",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: -2,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "2 * 242 = 484",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "Yes",
        correctAnswer: 484,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "6 - 7 = 1",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: -1,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "2 - 2 = 0",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "Yes",
        correctAnswer: 0,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "42 + 42 = 82",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: 84,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "13 * 3 = 33",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: 39,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "16 * 4 = 32",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: 64,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "9 - 1 = 8",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "Yes",
        correctAnswer: 8,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "66 - 65 = 1",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "Yes",
        correctAnswer: 1,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "23 * 2 = 48",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: 46,
        isVisited: 0
    }
];